printinghost.com 2010-09-27

# printing host has the policy to place your order for customized printing and privacy

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">PrintingHost.com is committed tomaintaining the confidentiality of our customers. We do not share, sell, orotherwise disclose information about our clients to any other party except asrequired to process and ship purchases. 

**<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Information Collection**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">PrintingHost is the sole owner of theinformation collected on <span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #000066;="">http://www.printinghost.com<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">. Printinghostcollects information from our users at several different points on our website.We use this information to improve the customer experience. 

**<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Registration**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">In order to use My PrintingHost, a user mustfirst complete the registration form. During registration a user is required togive a name and email address. We use this information to contact the userabout our services even if they have not placed an order.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Order**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">We request information from the user on ourorder form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email andshipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number andexpiration date). This information is used for credit card authorization and tofill customers orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the informationis used to contact the user.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Cookies**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’scomputer tied to information about the user. We use persistent cookies. Apersistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for anextended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by followingInternet browser help file directions.

Cookies are used by both the My PrintingHost and the PrintingHost order sectionin order to uniquely identify users, associate user files with orders, and toenable the shopping basket. Our site cannot be used with cookies turned off.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Log Files**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">Like most standard website servers, we use logfiles. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internetservice provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp,and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information foraggregate use. This data is not linked to personally identifiable information.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Communications from theSite**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">Special Offers and Updates:  
Established members will occasionally receive information on products,services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy ofour users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.If you do not wish to receive future emails, send an email to<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #000066;=""> remove@printinghost.com<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Customer Service**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">We communicate with users on a regular basis toprovide requested services. Both our production and customer service staff useemail and phone information to communicate with customers about issuespertaining to their orders.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Legal Disclaimer**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">Though we make every effort to preserve userprivacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by lawwherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to complywith a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served onour website.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Third PartyIntermediaries**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">We use an outside shipping company to shiporders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods andservices. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personallyidentifiable information for any secondary purposes.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Business Transitions**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">If PrintingHost should go through a businesstransition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of aportion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, bepart of the assets transferred. If as a result of the business transition, theusers’ personally identifiable information is to be used in a manner differentfrom that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistentwith our notification of changes section.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Choice/Opt-out**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our siteat the point where we ask for information. Users who no longer wish to receiveour newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving thesecommunications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or emailus at <span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #000066;="">remove@printinghost.com<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Links**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">Our sites may contain links to other sites.Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of suchother sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and toread the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personallyidentifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to informationcollected by this website.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Supplementation ofInformation **

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to thisprivacy statement on the homepage and other places we deem appropriate so ourusers are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and underwhat circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information inaccordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information ina manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notifyusers via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use theirinformation in this different manner.

If customers have opted out of all communication with the site, ordeleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor willtheir personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we makeany material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect userinformation already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice onour website notifying users of the change.

 **<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" #3f3f3f;=""> Contact Information**

<span 9pt;="" verdana="" ,="" sans-serif="" ;="" color:="" black;="">If customers have any questions or suggestionsregarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

   **info@printinghost.com**

 **USA Office:  
** 26645 W 12 Mile RD STE 201  
Southfield MI  48034-7812  
USA  
978-801-0205

 **Canada Office:  
** 5370 Longhouse Cress  
Mississauga, ON, L5R 4A5  
Canada  
905-756-2615
